so let's see if we can use the test and
right family of instructions to
implement locks the instruction we will
be using will be the test and set
instruction and its parameters are a
register and a memory address usually in
the form of offset plus a register what
test and set does is very similar to our
test and right in that it checks the
memory location at this address if the
memory relation is zero we put a 1 there
and we set our 1 to 1 if the memory
location was not 0 then we just set our
1 to 0 without writing to memory if we
have such a test and set instruction the
lock function for a mutex lock wire can
be implemented by setting our 1 to 0 and
then as long as our 1 is equal to 0
doing what